Guide to the George Pólya Papers SC0337
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2003-185
  - Two papers by Alexandre Wittenberg (in French), 1957 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Paper on "Structure-Counting Functions", 1958 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Institute for High School Teachers of Science and Mathematics, 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Social Aspects of Science, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Pamphlet "Synthesis" (in Dutch), undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Putnam Mathematical Competition, 1948-1949 (Box 2, Folder 38-40)
  - "Code Civil Suisse" (in French), 1907 (Box 2)
  - "Seminar Aufgaben" (in German), 1929 (Box 2)
  - "Aufirahme Porifung" (in German), 1935 (Box 2)
  - Notes (in German), 1937 (Box 2)
  - Daily Log Book (in German), undated (Box 2)
  - Draft of Pólya’s doctoral dissertation (in Hungarian), 1912 (Box 2)
  - "Vom Sternenhimmel" (in German), undated (Box 2)
  - "Twenty-Five Lessons in Citizenship", 1945 (Box 2)
  - "Federal Textbook on Citizenship", 1943 (Box 2)
  - "Buchbinderarbeiten" (in German), 1928 (Box 2)
  - "Biztositasi Szemle" (in Hungarian), 1955 (Box 2)
  - "Methode vol Laguerre zur Bestimmung des Geschlechts einer ganzen Funkton" (in German), 1914 (Box 2)
  - "Tolstoi" (in German), 1907 (Box 2)
  - "Biztositasi" (in Hungarian), 1956 (Box 2)
  - Unsorted papers (Box 3)
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2009-240
  - Correspondence (some in photocopy form, some to Gerald Alexanderson), papers by others, biographical articles, source materials on other mathematicians, and a few photographs. (Box 1)
  - Reprints and other published materials by Pólya and others (Box 2)
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2016-095
  - Materials from exhibit at Mathematics & Statistics (Math-Stat) Library, circa 1985-1987 (Box 1)